Guide to the New York Wine & Grape Foundation records, 1968-2004.
New York Wine & Grape Foundation records}
- Series X. Events
  - Letter-UPS, February 12, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - UPS Shippers, March 1987 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Distribution - Boston, Washington, Cleveland, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Disaster relief, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Trade networks, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Trade networks, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - New York food producers and marketers, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - New York Wine and Food promotion, November 1988 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Sparkling wine promotion, December 14 1988 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Wine Course members, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Wine Course, November 1988 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Wine Course, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Wine Course, new members, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Rainbow Room tasting, January 1988 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Media inquiries, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - New York retail stores, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Ontario Trade tasting, June 1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Restaurant requests, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Tasting inquiries, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Winery tour hours and events, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - I Love NY Spring Winery mailing, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - I Love NY Wine Country Spring Festival, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - I Love NY Wine Country Spring Festival, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - I Love NY Wine Country Spring Festival, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Uncork New York posters and oversize brochures (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Retail postcards, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - May 10 Wine tasting, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Table grape replies, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Table grape meeting, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Slides loaned, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - New York State Department of Economic Development, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Wine industry, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Beef booklet, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Place Wine Festival, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Cooperative Advertising program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - New York City events, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Events Questionnaire Buffalo and New York City, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Albany, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - California, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Export Promotion questionnaire, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Free-Standing insert, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Grape Juice program, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - New York Wine and Food promotion, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Retailers price wineries, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Tulsa, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - UPS international, 13 October 1989 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Wine Japan, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Wine trails, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Woodcliff Cap book, 6 February 1989 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - WSKG tasting, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - November tasting, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - In-Store tasting, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Wine and Cheese Classic Wisconsin Restaurant Association, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Korea-Taiwan trade shows, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Marketplace tasting, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Outdoor Events, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Wine, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Big Apple Festival, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Japan, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Laurentides, August 1990 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - LCBO Growing panel tour, September 1990 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Memorial Art Gallery tasting, 5 November 1990 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Wine Line, June 1990 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - New York Wine Line, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Wine Line final, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Wine Guide, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Wine Country Cal Info, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Calendar/Uncork, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Wine Industry Technical Symposium, cassette tapes, tr-10114-tr-10125 (Box 37)
  - Champagne Promotion, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Dallas Morning News National Wine Competition, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - General/Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Wineries, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Calendar/Contacts, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Ketchin Sales and Marketing, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Canada, ca. 1990s (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Exports, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Agricultural Service Market Promotion Program handbook, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Halifax, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Japanese market, 1990-1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Next winery mailing, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - The Society for American Wines, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Trade Shows, international, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - UK/Europe, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Albany events, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Networks, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Summer Internship program paper, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Wine competition, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Imports, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Rochester Events, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Glenora, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - Jim Tresize and HUD Secretary Andrew Cuomo, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - New York Wines promotional ideas, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Programs and events, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Windows on the World, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Wine industry, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Wine Vision, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Women for Winesense membership directory, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Publications, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 31)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Copies of the Living Section from the New York Times from 1990 have been removed, these are available online. They likely were saved because that is where the column Wine Talk by Frank J Prial is found.
McCarthy, Daniel. Pick the Right Wine, 1991
Cattell, Hudson; Miller, Lee. Wine East of the Rockies, 1982
Martin, Don; Martin, Betty. The Ultimate Wine Book, 1993
Quinlan, E. Michael; Pollock, Paul; Quinlan, Shannon. Wine Trivia, 1985
Posert, Harvey; Franson, Paul. Spinning the Bottle, 2004
MacNeil, Karen. The Wine Bible, 1984
Miller, Mark. Wine -- a gentleman's game The Adventure of an Amateur Winemaker Turned Professional, 1984
Lord, Tony. The New Wines of Spain, 1988
Clarke, Oz; Rand, Margaret. Oz Clarke's Encyclopedia of Grapes A Comprehensive Guide To Varieties and Flavors, 2001
Pavone, Christopher. The Wine Log A Journal and Companion, 1999
Perdue, Lewis. The French Paradox and Beyond: Live Longer with Wine & the Mediterranean Lifestyle, 1992
Turback, Michael. A Month of Sundaes, 2002
de Vito, Carlo. East Coast Wineries A Complete Guide From Maine to Virginia, 2004
Parker Jr., Robert M.; Rovani, Pierre-Antoine. Parker's Wine Buyer Guide 6th Edition, 2002
Winthrop Haeger, John. North American Pinot Noir, 2004
Zimmerman, Jan. Web Marketing for Dummies 2nd Edition, 2009
Pellechia, Thomas. Garlic, Wine and Olive Oil Historical Anecdotes and Recipes, 2000
Turback, Michael. Greetings from the Finger Lakes A Food and Wine Lover's Companion, 2005
Lichines, Alexis. Alexis Lichine's New Encyclopedia of Wines & Spirits The third edition of the classic work: fully brought up to date for the 1980s, 1981
Adams, Leon D. The Wines of America Third Edition, 1985
Bundschu, Jeff; Sebastiani, John; Sangiacomo, Mike; the Wine Brats Coalition. The Wine Brats' Guide to Living, with Wine, 1999
The Vineyard Almanac & Wine Gazetteer Fourth Edition, 1982
Lewis, Norman. The New Roget's Thesaurus in Dictionary Form, 1978
Stevenson, Tom. Wine Report 2006, 2005
Ford, Gene. The Benefits of Moderate Drinking Alcohol, Health & Society, 1988
Rayyis, Jamal A. Food & Wine Magazine's Wine Guide 2005, 2004
The Angel of Temperance Drinking in Moderation, 2003
Perdue, Lewis. The Wrath of Grapes The Coming Wine Industry Shakeout and How to Take Advantage of it, 1999
Gianotti, Peter M. Newsday's Guide to The Wines of Long Island, 1998
Clarke, Oz. Oz Clarke's Pocket Wine Guide 2002, 2001
Stevenson, Tom. Wine Report 2005, 2004
Stevenson, Tom. The Sotheby's Wine Encyclopedia The Classic Reference to the Wines of the World 4th Edition Fully Updated, 2005
Gianotti, Peter M. A Guide to Long Island Wine Country, 2001
Clarke, Oz; Spurrier, Steven. Clarke & Spurrier's Fine Wine Guide A Connoisseur's Bible, 2001
Wine Enthusiast Magazine October 2007, 2007
Wine Spectator October 2007, 2007
The Wine Spectator February 1988, 1988
TravelHost February 1996, 1996
Hudson Valley February 1996, 1966
Klees, Emerson. Wineries of the Finger Lakes Region The Heart of New York State, 2003
Bespaloff, Alexis. The New Frank Schoonmaker Encyclopedia of Wine, 1988
Zraly, Kevin. Windows on the World Complete Wine Course, 1985
Zraly, Kevin. Windows on the World Complete Wine Course Millennium Edition, 2000
Zraly, Kevin. Windows on the World Complete Wine Course 1999 Edition, 1999
Bespaloff, Alexis. Alexis Bespaloff's Complete Guide to Wine Revised and Expanded Edition, 1994
Thomas, Marguerite. Wineries of the Eastern States, 1996
Klees, Emerson. Underground Railroad Tales With Routes Through the Finger Lakes Region, 1997
Memorial Statements Cornell University Faculty 1997-98, 1998
Parker, Jr., Robert M. Bordeaux A Consumer's Guide to the World's Finest Wines Fourth Edition, 2003
de Treville Lawrence III, R. Jefferson and Wine Second Edition, 1989
Young, Alan. Chardonnay Your International Guide, 1988
Clarke, Oz. The Essential Wine Book, 1985
Duijker, Hubrecht. The Wines of Chiles, 1999
Borrello, Joe. Wineries of the Great Lakes A Guidebook, 1995
Epicurean Rendezvous Northern California 100 Best Restaurants, 1991
Sendzik, Walter & Waters, Christopher. Buyer's guide to Canadian wine Vines second edition, 2002
Atticks, Kevin M. Discovering Lake Erie Wineries, 2000
Klees, Emerson. Legends and Stories of the Finger Lakes Region, 1995
Ford, Gene. The Science of Healthy Drinking, 2003
Schneider, Steven J. The Internation Album of Wine, 1977
Martell, Alan R.; Long, Atlon. The Wines and Wineries of the Hudson River Valley, 1993
Cattell, Hudson; Jones McKee, Linda. Wine East 2004 Buyers' Guide Winery and Vineyard Equipment and Supplies, 2004
The Wines and Spirits of France, 1983
Reisch, Bruce I.; Pool, Robert M.; Peterson, David V.; Martens, Mary-Howell; Henick-Kling, Thomas. Wine and Juice Grape Varieties for Cool Climates,
Preszler, Trent Leon. Thesis Using Factor Analysis and Ordinal Logistic Regression to Model Perceptions of Ultra-Premium New York Wine Among Restauranteurs and Retailers in New York City, 2002
Johnson, Hugh. The World Atlas of Wine 4th Edition, 1994
Amorose, Michael A. A Catalog of California Wines 6th Edition, 1989
Reynolds, Kristian S. Finger Lakes Panoramas, 1999
Getz, Donald. Explore Wine Tourism: Management, Development & Destinations, 2000
Ginestet, Bernard. The Wines of France Saint-Julien, 1985